that a
[music]
Hello hello everyone what is my friends
I hope you are doing well
Welcome to Difficulties Live Episode of Ka
Visit Today with Discuss Afghanistan
Solid Mirchi Hall This Hair Lakshmi Went
Only Light Can See Jayashree Dharmaraj Waqt
Dharamraj himself is the joyous Sher Singh Rana
Divesh Kheera fame Stitching Singh Ninad
Forced Shubhangi Singh Ganesh Shiv Shankar Sudhir
Kumar Ani State Ironman Sonu Mandal
Pacific Island Anshuman Yadav Chandan came and every
Dungar Singh Chauhan
Shivdeep Arya Vikas symbol Neha Marta
suspect Ankit
Sujay Kumar Ghosh Hussain Sonam Singh Shankh Jeet
Ghosh and money more people good evening good for
Every great to see your wish Jyoti which you
kinda restless and like toe thank you thank you.
For Your Love Yourself Thank You For Your
Defeat of comment than thank you for the basis
of support for encouragement to really
Appreciate would also like to thank all the
Members that thing memberships toe support were
Chanel thank you so much thank you to all of you
He has contributed to the channel Ayurveda
Pal UPI Extra I really appreciate
A very great full thank you so much
so that they will discuss Afghanistan and
Politics and IF Pick Award-2009 Thirty
Questions Vighnash
Article 350A Vardhaman Today But English
Mat best so let's get intimate with
Question number one
Question number one is the question Kuldeep
Kaushik is only 9 cents away from the People of Rajasthan
The High Court
There are soldiers in Afghanistan and here
The question is something is not adding up hair
Tips Difficult People and In Favor of Sharia
Law and Order in the Earth on Spring End
More waiting to leave the country I don't thing
This simple request in Vancouver system.
Very good question Bihar to understand
If not WhatsApp then according to the point
Viruddh Naitik Last Year When Relationship
It's Route 99 on Cent of Nations People Are In
In favor of Sharia law, it dried what were
Sitting in the media news and loud
Meeting is Dubai Airport in Kabul Walking
Dead Trying to Escape Country and Good Two
Waste is Waste is Show the Question is Not
Consider Valid Questions a Som Benefit
Tutor population in favor of Sharia law who
And what which talks with Taliban is
Ghoul Pimples and Harold Imposed in Wale
Accidents desperate to leave the country
So let's understand why this show has a
Write a post and make anti-religious comments
Location and 250 Years Eve with busy options
For You in Mother Was
A Deep at Government
degree
College Government Imposed
By Gandhi
For
This government in various forms of
Various government machinery and
Subscribe
Tractors
People Who Passed Today
Ghrit Government and he's very busy
man in various ways 20 people will fashion
Form of Retailation Bluetooth
Taliban
Vipan listen later Chun more All want to leave
The Country
People Specially on English Playlist One
Cent Percent
Blood, Sweat, School, Bread, The People in Various
Universities in USA and
Academic
hot scenes in the
preparation of
the country and all
Subscribe and they don't care in
The Next Twenty Years in a Decade
of the
Country has been under the impression of being
Quiet Dravid and Infosys and With Self
Since 1979, this media has been a country
With the Prospects and Very Bleak People
I want to leave the country because I am not
Barrister Remembers and Wrong Turns of Multipurpose
Better future in the best while living a
Economic reforms where is this is a
Economic Migrants Rishi's Better Life Inn
The Best All in India or Someone Else
Anywhere But Afghanistan Situations To Bed
This note is by Shahriar Log, Editor, Afghanistan
Has been turned into hell after this time, various
Sources for Decades Tubelight Desperate Toes
Leave in this final year question is happening
AP flight mode de and district to be
Complex legs and Gautam hair improvement sharp
And effectively the media is only focusing
On What's Happening at Hamid Karzai Intern
Quantum Kabul based note focusing on
Forest witch country and people residing at
Night in the snow depression din oy give som
Where is the order for corrupt media is on the
Airport in Kabul inducted in the
The impression that all countries despair to leave
Virat definitely from 1000 people who tried
To leave this point in time instead of there
Country is not scrubbing 11 and so they have
To understand the media is very good at
Creating a Certain Assumption About
Perception which does not reflect the actual
Reality Underground and and oil and in were
Country Only Focus in One Location in Kabul
which that is pneumatic cutting is impression
Amazing at least according to the spool
Debit the maturity period population 99% and
Mode on shallow fennel that answers this question
Lax Point Question Number To Go
On Call with Three Questions in One
Swastika SEZ Upa is linked to Aadhaar
With Taliban and Against Them in Violin
Vadak Limit People 10 Pakistan Hair Oil
Switch from This and What Should We Do Omkar
So grouped in system that war 1328
SKX Reports of Indian Fighter of
Kerala has them of and Akash considering and
This is exactly what Airport Questions Arise is all about.
What is the 1622 in this had and can be
Counted as a Crucial Player, Dhairya Sudhi
I am on half leave in the middle of this question
Half of these are related to the Taliban and
and they related to Pakistan and the
Independence Players So Let's Get Solid
The history of this terrorist outfit has
Been on this or is still and Dasha Group's
Mat sometime now birthday golu in brigade
In the Middle East, Iraq, Syria, Arjun
Upright
and eventually off with few years they have
Report of a created strong room
Subscribe Now to Cash Withdrawal
Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi inside
90 and Shoaib Pakistani branch of the
thing is 84 cents of representatives to
Pakistan and they are able to create a
Bench of this Court in Pakistan in which Ali
al-Baghdadi
Video then subscribe to the people in
North West Frontier Province, Pakistan
Witch Mostly
Tours paste so precise
Words Think
More or Less Russian Like Leaders and Udham Singh
Ko bhi par stones and the objectives to
The Creature Guys license this character.
Stands for a little recipe and easy this
Summary of North Eastern Iran
Afghanistan Pakistan
and parts of
Population with no Pakistan right
Acid Provinces Uninstall Name Correction In
The world thoda sa comes from the Sanskrit
Situ In Situ Corrupt Media A Bit In
The resurgence of houses that I want to create
A Separate Autonomous Wah Elephant in the Khorasan
Regenerative actually give and honey and designs
Raees on India rate today this word is
This is the country and is not linked with Taliban.
Let him give the printer connected with Taliban
Pakistani Taliban and the bad Taliban and
Semen
Subscribe to Aadhi is involved in this
Sense of Well is like Spinners Everywhere
with any terrorist outfit hind meanwhile sexual
Sangatha Connection with Him with His Forces
Should show Ayush very rough it is very possible
The Possible Very Likely chapter is on the side
Odd sum of involvement in the activities
period against ISIS in this fierce
Bombing playing with equal airport
Two bomb blasts extended to 259 people.
trying to leave the country
I did this
Amazing Last Hut Morgan Hunting 71A
Prince Diane Besson 2012 American Soldiers
Died in that is
Servi Man of the Afghan Suicide Was Killed
In a result for sharing this American
Soldiers Drink After Listening to Things Happen
Show a that is the things oasis's this local
Terrorist Outfit Amazon Freshener Angad
The Major Players and the Taliban
Pakistan Pakistan Taliban Haqqani
The network has also targeted the Afghan Taliban, which has 920
Album These New Flavors of Terrorist
Attacked on Providence
Dushmani Different Areas to Operate with Anshuman
Especially in Pakistan should be
Amazing Collections with All of Tham Tuk Som
level and you all have the same ideology
World You Would Have Different Leadership Is
Ahmedabad and Leadership Drona People To Be Inn
Power objective want to come to power in name do
The Reason Sideshow These Conflicts Between
Lord and Uday date of Angry Birds IS
And the next question is a question.
Historical One Seems All This Must Begin
with the Soviet invasion of Afghanistan
Centre and Soil USSR Blame for
Disaster Afghanistan Situation as Much as
Dena Research and Wide Web Infrastructure
At any where constructed without consent
of the planets landmines already
Tubelight question cleared from this video
Martin Way: The Chocolate Hero in Afghanistan
Weeks weight topper than this village politics
Double Domination You No Matter How Much Territory
And Infosys has version of one more
The irresistible What Happened Is That in 1978
draupadi sharma xxx video hd
Print from Revolution Acquisition 1978
Dryad Officer Communist one over
Afghanistan is now divided into local communist parties and
And tow political outfits inside singer and Hafiz
Engineered Durable Goods
Power and Noble and to Very Short Period
of time or just three months or so this
Individual ki phir login thi only state
Where Water in Afghanistan Exacted
same mode of education for thousands of
Clans were worshipped as being opposed to
This ideological minimum socialism in Chapra
An order and he saw a political opponent.
This or Survey of Terror in Just Three Months
Sudhi
The Revolution Was a Communist Takeover
Afghanistan it was certainly Allah and
In favor of reverse repo when USSR
Revolution approach to blood ris zinc
Dros installed nav das gaye Hafiz Ghulam in
Image Somani Animation Jatin 3-If Situation
Bakem Very Volatile and Very Strong
Possibility Dubai counter-revolution
Account well in which this is highly unpopular
person in this highly un
Popular removed also vote rule and some other a
Political Dispensation Vote [ __ ] Toe Power
obligation
Seeing the question, he became a successful Brahmin.
Power but this crazy person Hafiz alarm in
The established in the country and definition
16 To Protect The New Found Investment
and the new password
Advantage in Afghanistan vs USA
Decide to
Invention and Secure Kabul Secure
Receiving confession subject is what
precipitated the
USS Invasion of Afghanistan enhancements
Foundation for your services in this also
Its future is being set up by fashion
Suitings Manpasand Soviet Invalid
Afghanistan gave over Kabul and a
Executive Officer Amin and Put Some Real
Selves in place and who has long and
Operation Di Yu used to involve Pakistan
This Mujahideen Steve Jobs created
Mujahideen Operative Great Freedom Fighter
Hero Splendor Every Rocky Movie Made in
which were appointed as freedom fighters
Fighting Switch and all that is yes sir to be
Blamed for the best situation noticed
If this is something
600 This famous acid The Video then
subscribe to the
Page if you liked The Video
then
subscribe to the Page
if
you liked the video then
subscribe to the
Video then subscribe to the
Page
Gandhi
Loot Pandit
What Future Came Before Seen of Compulsion
Thank Yourself in the Next Twenty
Years with Taliban Survivors Decade of
Governance for and video shown by the
Resistance against foreign invasion please
Answer
Suresh Vyas King is well Taliban Survive
updated in power at the governments who
Lives with Americans have the Taliban the best
Possible Chance and Surviving in Difficult Times
Toe Hand Over Country Over
Plinth Deficit End
billions of tens of millions of dollars of
Veterinary Channel
Subscribe
to definitely
Login and also possible Judge Vivek Puri Duty No
I Don't Thing a Coincidence Solid Looks
Like an American, the Taliban Devotees
Taliban to take over country amid Taliban
Security list should be kept in power at any time.
One brand name in Afghanistan and the country
of literacy in the International Women's Behad
United Nations level something morning Delhi
noida to dead things today what is the
The long-term objective of you is what they
Intend you have done December looks like a
Taliban in Actuality by Able to Secure
London Freewheel Difference Now Situation
In Northern Afghanistan, Zanjeer Wali
Dhairyadhar and Other Actors in the World
History Honours Physics Inside Pakistan S
us it's india also obscene level that
It is a complex situation but also possible
Inside the Taliban in White The Russians
Chinese and obscene walking then Taliban
Uddar Happy with the new government to the
and the government withdrew its
Sole Things and Tweet Volatile Situation
Quite True Leaders Now What Is Not
Inconceivable if the Taliban also able to stay
In Power for Decades and Even Today Girls
Students Unhidden
Display in how the International Committee
Specific Players The
Dhaliwal and how they are able to use a
Various forms will eventually want to
Extract that dear all want from witch
Country
Saw it's us in a
that Ashutosh this wide universe military leave
Behind 605 billion and worship place and system
Disturbance the whole Middle East a gross the
Best and opposite blender straight Americans
Don't See Afghanistan Add Part Dhammil List
Objective Miley to Dream Geographical
Region in country Sidhi Afghanistan Pakistan
Region s another good past record of park
which is the largest so called south
India the Vision in Americas
Sleep now leaving behind some
List Playlist In Any Way
Taliban comment on Bigg Boss
Subscribe
amazon middle aged man what is the
Turn off the value
quid definitely tens of millions of
How many dollars is possible from which
Taliban novels in possession of this weapon read
And its Rangers Taliban lost some people
Have been reported the Taliban have been
Sending hypnotized Pakistan that is not
Prakash Taliban Mill's Problem Sales Na
He is on the same account of power struggle of solid
Debit
Ronit Roy to Consolidator Hold and Taliban
Debit Pakistan and Mini Statement
Devi Try And
Destroyer and Established Himself But
Hey the pass
Patience Will Want to Interest Taliban
Chinese 124 Taliban American Homes Will
Want to Win
Win a thrilling draw with American Sacrifice
And so much they spray Shanidev in their horoscope
and Taliban to be free to time distant
From external influences for instance
in the Pakistani
Taliban Everything with Taliban Old
Everything to Pakistan to scream after
Benazir Bhutto, the ISI's audit officer,
and bioscience pakistani girls using
American President
When the Taliban
destroyer1 after pakistani meanwhile dutt
Pandey's 100 Pakistan Pakistan War
Middleman and all his weapons for rent in India
Wedding is a time when the Taliban and
Benefiting from this reformed Taliban
completely under the control of the
Pakistanis
Na Va Chhappan is that in the absence of anyone
Registered a minute ago, the country almost
overnight and have come into operation of all the
Swapan 385 Builders Parisar W Vipan Reed End
So much Ashwani Tomar, let's thank you to it
Like the Here and Now Legitimate Government
Almost these days it depends on Pakistan
Some extent specially the Chinese girl in
Board interested in board with Chinese
Interest Dongari Involved Pakistani Foreigner
Jamshed was a Pakistani judge at this time.
Side against each other
10560 Americans Clearly Unwanted Taliban
Toe Break Free From Pakistan Toe Mon
Extent
Choice of the disturbance found 372 edits
Seems like a disservice to observe the
Taliban Illegitimate and Strong Political
Player Geopolitical Player Sensory
looks like that was the intention to
symbol of
Porn What Exactly Is Backing Super
POWER WITH US UN CHAKRA POWER FAMOUS
Certificate Examination is not being run
By terrorists officially united
States only Major Super Power Derogation and
Power lines they have engineered the situation in
Which nation in the recent events of the nation
was handed over to destroy his own
Plotter Devendra Chaudhary Left Behind
Billions of tens of millions of dollars worth
of veterinary and amount of cat and much more
Mission Arms and Men's and Possibly School
Supplies and what not the American and this
And the United Nations is like it's nothing but
instrument of powerful countries like
usa z f hello how do you still control
Yu N Morgan Morgan Chinese Yuan It
Porn not getting involved in the central
Reshu Jain will lecture India on Kashmir but
Deol's point is what the qualities of
Taliban that is reality now united
Denomination of Nations Now Input Tax
Seriously you yourself are not involved in this
Apart from eating something this in the USA is
Not Powerless US Can Be Taliban Talks
To next present want to days June 2012
New Delhi Dam Country and Plate Sudhir Sam
long-term your political game being pledged
of today also right now in your order current
Vishwas Dum but Lee Space Create a Just
Watch What's Happening
Big Americans definitely have a long term
Planned Parenthood in This Part of the Process
handing over marks 22 Taliban without
Any Any Real Resistance
Sunset Country Is Not Being Run By
Terrorists officially may be very soon
Destroys the Nation also removed in the
I also boil considered to be given the title
of the illegitimate government in its message
But in this he is also junior in maximum
Maximum two years is also included in the memorandum.
Sonar Deals Situation Not Long Term Your
Political games have been played on equal grounds
Engineer Day by Users
yes yes sorry bunny now
Aman a what you have
these were
midnight with me
The
Air Force Base Night Without Informing
Half Velvet Afghanistan Inn
computing for
Planning Department
subscribe
The Amazing
Differently Abled
Subscription Looking Very Nice
looking directly in front of
Camera
Latin Americans
The Buddha may be Situation and Choda Welling
TukTuk Fullest Look
Invested there profits of some kind of
long-term joe building game it is very
Clearly, look at the children into
Liquidation Meaning Stupid Lekar Handsfree
Munch Pulao Research and Tubelight Na Ho In The
Man of the Match David
Dhawan
More
People shopping which used to
inside
Faith in the Middle East
Delhi Delhi
End
Slowly Slowly In
Orderly Manor So es To
Display board this voice mail
Should support in bikini with Uday
Channel Ad So Ye People Who Acted Hai
American businesses drop special limit visas
texture is paper work for the American jis
translators and they stop in embassy and in
Various Other Other Raw Capacity 200
People Have Kids of December 10, 2019 Months
for two months in the middle of people in the
middle of living in the
Middle
Of the night with her boobs
To choose not to avoid
subscribe to the Page
that Sudhir Vision for the Best protest notice
Gas set battery in the name of Arjuna Award
Saver mode on, it will be accurate
More clearly in Begum line but this is clearly
E M of
Assistant Plan Which Is Which Which
Country Skiing Infection
And the next question is The Voice India
Alarm of Muslims come to India 1037
Islamic Countries Do Good and Evil Not
Cause Problems for India in Future CEO
India is not opening its doors for all
Exams to come in, now fans want to
Come to India in the past even deeper
Najibullah Refill Mini Form of
Members were given refuge in India
Deodar Living in Delhi Even Today I Think
Members of the Family Members Period
Government official cycle
Today India is not opening its doors.
Comment and Kamlesh and Ladakh India has given
Asylum to Very Specific Very Talented
Individuals
Just a Handful of Individuals Wear
Mostly for MP 20 and Afghan Professional
Work as staff in Divya Indian Embassy such
People who truly connect with India and
Certain people from different youth governments
Members of Parliament and Prov
Itself but two three do and model 500 very
Small Selected for People Who Have Been
Offered asylum in India have been
Evacuated to Afghanistan and Indian Air
Force Slice inside in Indian and recent
Vihar Terminal T-3 and Demo Martyrs' Day
samu songs mp3 female
MP4 com * India Voucher Key Wise Bhole Ji
Inch Extra * Enter India and Seek
Asylum Seekers Deposit of India with
Clear the Indian Government has very
Specific plan, very specific set of
Individuals with synonyms of Wasallam
India it's not open to everybody last
days minutes apart thousands of people to just
Walking the Country Is Not Left
Front four wheels currently do not have any open
Border with Afghanistan also helps
In the morning, able to handle with people, this fool
and the Afghanistan war people coming other means
Ready to be deported toe it's not
In most situations, even in the suppressed media.
Report Namak Wah Media Saying That He
Certainly not free fall and fennel and banana
Situation VR Hand Painting Just Small
Number of Hindi videos to come into India
That
Abhishek Asks What Should Be Tajikistan
Soil in Afghanistan Anti Taliban
Rebels and Diocese of and Northern
Alarms Join Hands to Destroy Anyone
other is taliban ok so answer this question
Viewers in Tajikistan
The meaning of you may not have been very clear
About It Is It Means Share The Map And
Demons Twist Places
Near the map of the series India vs.
India, Jammu and Kashmir
Gilgit-Baltistan Pakistan Share
subscribe and
subscribe
comment and
don't know what
Should be Tajikistan in Afghanistan
No Taliban
Don't forget to subscribe
Scientific Place
So and Vinod Kumar Afghanistan this butterfly
Tajik papa peepal earn Indo-Iranian pepal
Stones on the right foot speak with every
Language Amazon for formation in the army
Soldier Movie Capacity Mentor Director
Principal Sister and Brother Sister Inn
Different Amla Saale Easier For Example And
So S Ahmed Masood on the side Ahmed Shah Masood
Nikita cleans her panties, causing Afghan soldiers to
Tajik Minority
Decimal in Northern Afghanistan
And possible to Pakistan definitely has
Infinity wor on the people will definitely try
And help them with reduced Taliban
Shaun Tait on this aspect Tajikistan Road Indore
Ko too we supplies coming in father for the
Lines from Tajikistan in the form of an eye
Show supplies and weapon re and ammunition and
fuel
Kunwar Japendra Possibility of Life in
English word meaning in Tajikistan scroll
These nine days of very short dialysis
lines on hand
Suggestion to Fight Against Rate of Minimum Wages
Taliban I don't
See The Reliance and Joining Hands with Ice
than this
Zameen Vinod Lions Club in Government
Jobs
Dashrath Government in Delhi
With a Belief Masood
Subscribe
Government
in Delhi today
Ideologies Very Different
World Very Different The Future They Want
From Afghanistan is very different Amen
Is K and Vinod lines to I will not see
any possibility
Aaf Dum Joining Hands and Fighting Taliban
Taliban John * Reliance failed attempt
Life is different in Taliban-zone countries
outfits in groups in the world in this but
It is highly unlikely in my opinion for
The ISS's Toe Join Hands With No
Gidhour Alliance to specific Taliban
Excerpts from Health You Are Not Able To
In the early elimination of the Taliban
Decades
that he Alvand this was invalid Afghanistan
In twelve without you must be able toe wipe
Out was the Taliban presence in most
Afghanistan Right Sudhir W and Four Decades
after years for
conducting a military operation against
Taliban Afghanistan
conducted during this time which will be
Conducted on road price in Pakistan
But they don't see the source and
Taliban Pakistan
American Not Go After Real Source
Taliban
America
Taliban and Pakistanis
Well Known Toe
You doing quid not want
Taliban to be destroyed, the news
Taliban in a Pakistani army and causing
Death of Thousand Soldiers Fighting for You
Should
have died in the last 2 years in
Taliban and Pakistan in Afghanistan
Army in various games in New Delhi -
110 American Research Does Not Destroy Taliban
Taliban
Issue
Subscribe
long-term game
play karo
[music]
That
Squeezed the overhead tank from time to time
The Taliban further this lineage that bags this show 250
The Americans know full well if the Taliban this
Alive and well it is it is the proving a
cross-border to South in Pakistan
Taliban
Navodaya Navodaya
Dungar Singh Chauhan
Subscribe Politicians Should Remember Not
For Criticizing Joe
Account you what is no political condition of.
my video channel
Subscribe The Channel
This
Planning in Power and Global
influences on
Seems to Be and Significant Decline and
Viewers Influence in Central Asia were
Two Pakistanis face off in Afghanistan
Bermuda Chinese Camp Log In Yourself Ons
Declines studied and significantly in this
Region Hindi Afghan-Pakistan Vision
with Chinese and rising if
Strings and power under the influence of
Finalizing
Soil us seems to be a divine power
Ventures into giving power to the reader
overall
well-being picture that reflects the political condition of
The United States of America
Aditya is from the Republican Party.
0.5 and shepherd is joe biden if decision
Maker in what Joe Biden discloses
2006 This Very and Early Person Hindi
dictionary of knows what he was doing inko
Day function here into our country
Electronic Iron Suzy The Something
Different Country and What We Call the
Country
which state is the
Tarzan the State Department Department
The Time He Industry
Corporation
unfulfilled desire
Not Doing Something Which Starts Indefinitely
Tense
Clearly Not Worth It
Not fit to be built clear so
Acid Wave Raw is a famous diva from Forex.
Policy Cancellation State Department of Birth
Various Times by Department When
Used once it has been very easy for superficially
Mode interested in having times like
Very strong in the present himself
was very strongly in control of foreign
policy but also for AIDS there was no
He had the power to dictate foreign policy.
In this prestigious Drishti GBU
Swift's mark saw this judgment of mine
Janam Legi Hai 108 Is Bollywood Have To See
In Brief Note Joe Biden Lemon Needs
Clearly IS NOT at its best
Saffron Akhand Free Middle Counties Definitely
Eclipse Very Confident Lee Corrections and Labels
Prank you sir vivian number from the governor of
Field Sector Jobs for the Countries with
The State Department is therefore in charge and
Happening with foreign policy level in
Afghanistan, Pakistan and other places
Such countries running smoothly and delivery no
What you are doing for a long term plan is
In Ayush and against not reported at
Bangladesh 3 inches to end Indians have been
Doing time in this pious soul not
Understand What Happened in 1971
Today It's People Rather Than Trees and Belief
Midnight 100 Billion
People from Bangladesh have been complaining
Toe Meet
you are
The
Country head calls Pakistani donkey
subscribe This is not in Bangladeshi
10 Mukti Bahini Against Pakistani Bandh
Inner Country
India Also Believe
90 A
Hello viewers what happened in 1971 in
Bangladesh
Drops Genocide Going on the Pakistani
Army that Genocide War People Who
Undervent
Minimum one million people died most likely
3245 million Bangladesh has decided to
Pakistani Specific Genocide The
Bangladesh was helpless as nothing would happen
Defend Themselves is the Indian
Established in the Indian Army Dedicated
This and Graduation Course Book Mukti Bahini
See Read Your Graduation Day Train These People
The Zara Tag Bubbles Dana
Dhund send them back into Bangladesh to fight
Rebellion against Pakistan years but
Unless the Indian Army in Indian Air
Force Center Visit
Dabangg Dwibhuj Never Have Held In Him
Sixes Dev Ne Var He Begum Junoon It Is The
Indian Army Internet If Everything But One
Day Or Mukti Bahini Header Minimal
Influence in Operations
There is Country Today Indian Army Nobles The
Mukti Bahini this justification that printed
Why is the village far away? Litmus Saeed Akhtar India
want to convert country to Pakistan and
Basically Disappearing Pakistan From
Diarrhea Control Pakistan100 1971 Vas
Not a rebellion Bangladeshis
Dabangg Aashiq Mahal will now put a plate in these
Food Recipes on the Side That You Don't Ignore
Vriddhi r country on the road difficult to
Revolt against Taliban and will again be
Scene shoot message now answer note am define
Population civilian population is not armed
With Taliban have machine guns were Pandit
Devendra AK-47 and he is a recruiter
Anybody Price Rise of But
It's An That Light The World Is Different
Plessis Inn
The world and real different boli ab gun
Point Office Dust World Changes 24 Against
and in no position to revolt against
Taliban End
100 grams melted
Wanted to give
Divine Slate Government
Was quite corrupt government does not only
Order Today
Justice in
Subscribe Taliban People Will Impose
serials
Subscribe
For Justice Will Give Something
Happy
Daughters of Government Rule 10
Subscribe to Change for Most People
Karastan to I don't see any reason why the
Revolt Against Taliban Rhythm
That Vinod Last How is this Taliban Group
Different from the Taliban
Schezwan sauce that is very interesting
Questions etc. 1996 Taliban Volume Medieval
Period of wisdom which were completely
Closed to the World They Did Not Give Press
Conferences and Craft for the New
Taliban Dravidian tech-savvy and AR very
Eager 200 Canopy Aadhar Card Image Want To
Project World De Yaar Bahut Der Officials
People Sportspersons Who Give Press
Conferences will ask for the right things.
Allah Woman Today Will Also Went World
Will Give Rise Toe Women Will Give Justice Toe
Everybody will remedies to be rose hearted
Americans Jaisingh Write Things in Black No
white noise
Deposit media channels CCTV of China and
RTO Inspector
Half Al Jazeera &c 910 writing columns
In The Washington Post The New York Times
According to Samsung American Newspaper
Simple equations have enormous significance
Diplomatic Corner Diplomatic PR
APR Good Know and This Clearly Elements
of media in two busy ashar involved in
This will be a very different Taliban one
Mote service Taliban diya tweeting on
Accounts on regular basis back to three
Twitter is the digital zone BlueStacks but dip
That pain is active on Twitter and so where
Is very easy weakness I am well played well
Thought Out Confronted Media Campaign Public
Relations camp in the middle that nice day
Understand How the Best Work for the Man of
The best way to help media houses is through this.
Tham To Som Extant Sudhir Va To Project
Certain Image of Doms Which May Not Be
reflected in the ground level and in
Speech Republic of Speech Medicine Taliban
Shanti all but in this is happening in the
public domain
Pimple Taliban reform project in
Pain is image office more progressive.
Slightly More Liberal Mode on Rent
Presumed Dead Difference
3996 Ground Level Late Mat Same Day Windows
10 Enterprise Him Butati Dham Is The Best
But do not take care of the day deposit
asset image into her life in the
The World Twitter
Video then
subscribe to the Page
If you liked the video then
subscribe to
Om Shri Jiske Chaugi Jo IS Corruption Has
Claimed recent bomb blast near Diwali
International Airport during their May Bay
Tha asi roll behind this is a
Possibility of yogic sciences in almost
Every terrorist organization is
Active in this area
White poison solve connection with this so called
S Khorasan Siddha Suni Detergent Fee
Different flavours and different facets of
Badher Ideologies MW Se Rate
Objects That Are the Same
Sound Idea Aircel definitely stupid
Udham notification bomb blast which he pointed
Triveni Taliban People Fall 9 Taliban Never
Killed American Soldiers Died as Information
And number of again quid guys trying
Toe Escape the Country and the Best Toe
Innovate He Built For Mrityu Deepali
Born or Any Other State of the Apes
Navodaya Official Statement This Dussehra Science
Fiction film Responsibility for the Attack
And the Taliban Drops of Lemon Day celebration
these were
So this is sexual a possibility what they want
Development
Officer removed from the Constitution * Its The Country and
Exclusive American on They Want To
Soldiers
Solitaire Finaly Bigg Boss Possibilities
If benefit in ISI
Also use this outfit on the web, you can try it
Sa Na Tu Triangle Control Taliban 94152
Try 9Bread for free if you get these apps
There is also another tool in the arsenal that continues
Toe Hold Capsicum Salt Mark
Quality Testing
Left Weapons Withdrawn from Loot Preetesh Creatures
in all set
For Watching the Question
Tajikistan
for brother in law
India The Amazing
Tajikistan Indian Air Force and Roting
hormones
Look back to Lotus Ayurveda India and
India is
Subscribe
Subscribe to
Ko share also a Tajikistan I think for air
Base System Where Near By
Two is the
what is the
what is the meaning of
This Aini
Subscribe Share Like This
And Sudesh looks like a proper air base
Vaccine Tajikistan and Senior Hangus
very good keep fighter planes
You to see some helicopter share on the Sharma
a pan couple of aircraft but i don't see
Sukhi Lal Jhanda Projects in the Very Good
Very good e decided but certificate land
of Sukhoi-30 aircraft on this a gift
Should I Indid One Is the Gift for More Words
Related to conduct for more
that they are the match pandey locator okay this is
and experts Tajikistan acid developed a
Clear Not White Operational From What IS
E
Who is not what extent India is
Operating
Absconders
presents
subscribe Video not support
Understand
by the way
on the Indian Air Force Effective
December
2009 Like Share The Voice India
Everything is the media Indian media IS
Currently in India meeting at India
Hotspot on rolls of yogini but I am
Really sorry for that is India plane mode
Turn Point Afghanistan and Tajikistan
Adhipatya Shroff Ling India Scars is the
thing at this point in time India is
More innovative and channel situation Iraq
War and People and Eyeliners Hum
Afghanistan in these days Begum Level Will
Play Some Cards and See How Do
Understanding India only playing as being
involved in any significant
Verification It's Too Early for Indian
Bluetooth Settings and Verify Sodium A
Rebellion in a Couple of Days When Will See How
Things go in the get into effect autonomous
Ego When Required
Slices what rule 10 terrorism in
Politics Apart from Suffering in Rural
and urban services at least to family
Group warrant government control what can
Be Done
and can be seen from a distance of
Galaxy Terrorism Please Significant Role
Indian Politics from the 1978 Thanks
Arvind Established His
Ides of Numbers See More 2019
Dal Now Dal Group In Live Withdrawal Divya
Russia Middle East Region
Siddheshwar Group targeted the Americans
Side Think in Western
Edison and vote this research decrees variance.
Powers with Dars USSR Year-old Sun
Chinese The Hum Aur Loop Reduce of Various
terrorist organizations to achieve certain
Geopolitical Objective The American News
Pakistan a proxy against India in
Pakistani news various states of these
Provision in India for more employment
Day Toxins Drink Year Kashmir War
1919 All Videos Question in India Even
During the United Khalistan thing in
North East Chinese Innovation in Sponsoring
And a supportive this varied.
Naga terrorist outfits which is
Very well documented
Wash clean and very very easy from here
Definitely News Channel Short Pitch
Definitely used in politics to wedge
against countries to make our country but
Subscribe to India News Middle East Region
boil
Sure orders from the Middle East Indian
Time to subscribe to our channel
Tow Consider Tow Bay Time Completed Time
Definitely one of the
Tools in the Political Toolkit
Player Significant Role
Assets Americans User IS
In the Middle East and stairs nurkh de
Tuesday Al Qaeda Against Devices Mind
Licenses
Insurance recovery is immediate
Which is why traffic control, which producers
Dip it in what a Sudra is blitting
Research
A militant group does that when the Power Rangers
Power Vacuum One
Rogers Poway Criminal Geographical Region
Local Lad Local Thak Janlokpal Gangsters Will
Rise up internet surf very good that
Dwarf
punch
Jagdish Return Gift Rolls Royce Out Of
Power Vacuums and You Have Big Players
Super Power for the Country's Debt Sponsor
On the other side it has News Room for various
Political
urgently
subject-wise
Payment to reduce rise in havaldar sustained
And the world, I certainly control Bajrang
Romance debit the number of chief operating
officer sitting printed pink controlling
Cool controllable with Taliban software
Englishman Brave Wright's sign is Libra
Strong then Pakistan everyone to control
Wali in this day control funding to control
The surprise of the nation would you like to
No everything was under Pakistani control
No white sesame seeds
that forest and government not able to control
See the room and enable to control the values
Loose and religious growth Strauss and mixture
salt well
Middle years from land acquisition for very
long time
What can be done to prevent them from
Forming oil does not add power back into
Form for example in India so this condition
Mano Asteroid Facts in Various Places
To visit in the government did not pay
Attention to Certain
Residences The Particular Fuel Surcharge To
Influence the Absolute and Destroyed
The Symbol
off power tariff
in
It's Natural
50 controlled by
Dars On
Switch from Jhalal 5 to So Much Instability in
Afghanistan, Pakistan, New Zealand and
Pakistan in Unison Falling Into the
Hands of Tehreek-e-Taliban Pakistan
Taliban and gave this
Oil requirement c any possibility of
Pakistani Nuclear Weapons Falling Into
The Hands of Retired with the Stars
Nuclear weapons were prized possession of
Pakistan and Beam It Is The Only Thing Which
Prevents India from steel rolling
Pakistan it is the life widening gives vat
give the distance of
Invulnerability
blurred and
Tehreek-e-Taliban Pakistan
Ne Butt
It's
Limbs where do it
This very strong and powerful weapon works
If Pakistani Punjabi gave loan, God loan
Chahiye Pakistan 2nd year country der andar
Country the all-powerful by develop of this
To happen due to ungli possibility of Sachin
Happenings in the Pakistani Army
Itself from different but very very
Unlikely Unless Electronic Force Under
Power Engineers Demise of Sir Actor
Pakistani Army Canteen Sach kah00n Shor
If Nuclear Weapons and Secured Before
Pakistan disintegrates from the beginning
You
Sleeping Girl Extremely Unlikely If
Pakistani Nuclear Weapons and Fall Into
The Hearts of Taliban and Any Dar
Terrorist outfits are highly unlikely now
Point Time
That
Abhinav Services India Edition To Not Have
Both Underground Afghanistan vs John
Right as India still not in opposition to
project power off side
100 questions is used in India the winter
Wind Minutes Early Intervention
and should not have
Not interested literally India has not been
Show cents to stop money location settings
Request in the best Hindi
For India to send mystery continues to
Afghanistan
assistant peacekeeping operations and
susyqu4tro
Government to support the
Show me the question for India
Is India wanting to send shoulders with
Indian Army Chapter to Afghanistan
What World India Benefits From Its
Units and Odd or Even People Today in R
Country Until Way Research Significant
Benefit for Your Country and Funeral Inn
Forests End
West is where India is not in a position to
Supply Serious
Diseases Jammu and Kashmir
Jammu and Kashmir
To
Pakistan has snatched the bud of Kashmir from Pakistan
Today India is not having access to
Afghanistan
India World Airlift Fussar
that and put them in Afghanistan day how
Did India supply religion and India send a
Surprise You All Food Food Material For All
Indians and definition of imagination and
Guys Things You Need A Syrian Army
Tips on Logistics the Army Is Not About
Only Fighting Chamak Registration Army K
Not fight elections and manor without
Logistical Supply Routes
Chagi Tips and Without Land Access to the
Country India cannot support itself
Hypothetical and Mean Afghanistan Logistics
19 sensitive almost in Indore
Activists and mission to send your
Shoulders of Clans Oil When You're Not In
A position to continuously and reliably
Sustainability
Reply them as and when required inside
for it's not a good idea this was not a
It was a good idea to send its soldiers.
In tow Afghanistan War Peacekeeping
process and and your fitting so Taliban
Even in the Kargil conflict, India and this
used you cross the border
Inches in Wedding, Pakistan Troops Back in
The Royal Enfield Harmon Pakistani Sa
Oil Indian Government Reduced Taxes
And Indian soldiers seven inches on points
Into Pakistan Territory
of India Versus and Dissolution
Ganistan and Vinod Dhoiye Root of Father
Crops in Pakistan own ignorance India
would not have been able to eliminate
Example: Indore 108 makes no sense to Gonda
Responsible and proper from Afghanistan
Military E A time-bound objective of bus
Similarly, divided into becoming cement MLAs
of the IPKF situation in Sri Lanka that came
Think when very good center India did not
Saint Soldier
Reporter Been Very Good Hearted to That
Fennel Whatsapp Is The Best Possible Outcomes
of India considering all the winter situation
Not Real Situation Interview Mother
India has not been built up its ability
Toe Protect Power Beyond Borders of
Indian
Politicians give way to victory over
Pakistan Inn
The Indian Army is a strict military force
Widron
It is up to the time light condition in place of
India has intervened to release on
have and watch is the policy in which is the
Correct Policy Adopted A
that now world politics is the people
Afghanistan love India and Indians so is
The Possibility to Reunite Afghanistan
Shades in Indian Territory
is distant from lots of people
10 Minute People Love Comedy from If People of
Lord Ganesha and Love India Hindi Indian
Media is not a sentimental Devgan love
India and Northern Alms Loves India
Certain Politicians of Friendship India
Leaf force is
According to the Pupo
99th place of St. of the People
Desire Aishwarya Love
you understand what is the tomorrow
Remind Me Indicates What Is The World
The viewer
Don't tell me cancer, people love India.
A simple question on
That teacher Shiva is one people want confluence
another country i'm glad to give very deep
Connection 9 Definitely Add DNA Connection
Between India and Pakistan Birthday
The report was submitted between the connections
India and Pakistan crows
10 Pakistan Live India Then Decide Shad
Sunday marked the 9th in Pakistan's most recent lead.
India the absence of senses
But their culture is the same as in Pakistan
So What Makes Indian Singers Against Love
India I know India sprint billions of
Dollars in Afghanistan Building Dams
Generation Rose Ann Parliament House Normal
Water India Chief that in India want to
Achieve some kind of love that people
that alternative Shab-e-Gham place in Afghanistan
today is such that
Watch Never Love India
12 People Bangladesh Growth Rate Cultures To
Must do Chaugane Student To India
9th People Gathered Don't Have Any One
Playlist One India The Delhi Police For
Pakistan and India Today
Khurshid Younger Generation of Good People
Saw this ID is unique in 10 countries
In India with People Afghanistan Love India
That is a very misplaced idea
That fans have no love for India did not feel
Any one for India don't see the world from
The perspective of DNA mode think they are
The Descendants of Lost Juice Crib
Most Ghanshyam and In Common with Middle
Eastern and Western Key and with Which
The country is India
Sorry for the time trap, three centuries on
words Afghanistan officially such thing to
Be a part of India during the time of
Ahmed Sham's note Amit and you during this time fruits
Ahmad Shah Abdali A
A State Subject Matter of Concern Officially
Became a separate country had suffered culture and
No that glass Hindu people six have left
Afghanistan Peacock and Lace
Notification for Digvijay Cultural Tizen
Mode switch off for foreign countries including Rajasthan
Now understand that question is very
Different 239 cultural activities under the bridge
No love for India, India he took in the same
Level S New York Oman & Qatar & Saudi
Arabia That Is The Collector Of The Nation Live
Show with sentiments of the people of Ganeshan
Love India and misplaced sentiments
Not love India and want for India rate
Cultures Almost Se Mute Se Agriculture
Pakistan Drone Lily Allen Daya Online Vid
India to submit its victims in 10
Now in this era Pakistan Pakistan Pakistan
Access Caricature Rupert Celebrity Kids
Where is the only vision Divyansh has been
Along with India Vikas Vihar and frustration
Apart from the No Love for India Please
Understand
Any Possibility to Unite Against Taliban
And in the next one hundred years at least
Give them this quarter inch to B
Project Will Take More Than a Hundred Years
It's Possible to Reunite Afghanistan
Different
But love you all the best
It happened ok Mr Jain says can you explain
Pakistan Iran Relationship and Can Iran
border with Pakistan
Kandy Iranian border with Pakistan Bay
Used to send Balochistan Freedom Fighters
Afghanistan might poll them the Taliban
Afghanistan has fallen in the Taliban
already
On the Question Investing in Around
When is Mother's Iran Support the Balochistan
Freedom Struggle Against Pakistan
Now Understand Yes Okay Lucky The Map
All these thoughts are about this country, the body and it is western.
Pakistan Frequency The Mouse Pointer No
That is not the only part of Balochistan haze
Yes followers of Chabahar during this morning
Port pooran is Indira Indian nutrition and
Balochistan Sindh Balochistan region is
Occupied by two countries like China and
Pakistan
Balochistan Freedom Struggle Against Intellect
And health power understand
Say Yes Location People Want Freedom From
Pakistan and also from Iran
Sunidhi Balochistan Freedom Movement Games
Ground in Pakistan it also
Represents a threat to Iran
Inside for Iran 10 not support the freedom
Struggle of Balochistan the day set against a
Selection of freedom struggle as attract
Desi Balochistan Freedom Fighters
Terrorist Uday It's Something Pakistani
Military Iranians Have in Common With Both Wants
To keep Balochistan subjugated is the
Pakistani pop Balochistan Chabahar is the
Read Iranian in Balochistan that Bluetooth
of this country is or occupying
Balochistan
Siddhavat is the truth
Sold in the border with Pakistan can not
Be used to set the system date
C
The situation is
loot
Shri Krishna Sage and
Acid in the previous episode India should
Engage with Taliban is possible in India
Should see what is the best possible toe
Approach long-term post Chop One Thing That
India will never be able to right that loose
Haze Taliban Will Be Totally Uncalled For
Example
Idli
Idli with Pakistan in the final give
to do do do
these directions situation what you are asking
Krishna is the most looped Taliban had
Waters Taliban What is the influences
Paliwal to understand what is the
Language in influence over Taliban will
Have to understand what the Taliban want
What is Active?
1515 I understand that we can understand
what forms of which can be used on
Suta Lee Dam First of All Want Toe
Secure your country they want to stamp out
All Opposition
Political Military This chapter and
Opposition to them with Taraf Institute Saudi
And Northern Alliance chieftain youth place that is
Them Still Exists and Still Fighting
for others on this subject want to stop
This is a position that secondary level want to
Established a Legitimate Government and
Again international recognition as
Legislature Government Afghanistan Issues
Want to reader country imposed and form for.
Alleged involvement in the country and they
Want to fight for reservation free and they
Have sufficient strength, physically strong
Hold in the country e
[music]
1200 is the Pashtun National Research and the of
Qualifying Day North West Frontier
Provinces and Pakistan and Afghanistan
So this is for long term territorial
Disputes with Pakistan if you long
Term Objectives
that he has the Taliban in the politics
long-term
Taliban video Pakistan Nagar Chinese Don't
Care over Pakistan in Chinese want to
Listen to Expanse of Thrones want to my
Afghanistan were and Extra Lithium D
Villiers Minerals Copper and What Not Between
Afghanistan has plenty of
University dec14 that slogan was these
State Book
The question is the Taliban
Direct Channel A Reliable Partner Taliban
No the
Mystery sleep give and imposing and yellow end
Desi Voucher Islamic Research Board Exam
Brothers President and A New Word Signs
of doing in East Turkestan Xinjiang
Region to two a good people in the then Taliban
Will Not Have One Feelings Va Jhalda Will
Certainly I'm Alive Extra Inter Short
term
In Exchange for International Recognition
Relieving Digit Christ International
Love results for the government suicide in this
Z2 of may willing to offer that is Taliban
Alarms China to engage with other countries in
Mining operations and web tuesday country.
Such transit routes for the now stand road
project
So the Taliban will definitely need a Chinese for
sometimes so in the short duration of time
In the next five years, baby
Badminton years with Chinese will have
Significator Mode Switch Over Taliban
Picture Pakistani Level Don't Worry Fast Di
Rasulallah Vriddhi Chinese Darshan Chinese Bhel
The Best Leverage India Will Not Have The Machli
Bridge also spent the next 3 years at
INVESTMENTS LEAN A 12345 BHAIN IS JAIPUR TO
The Last 3 Years Will Definitely Love Targeting
the Pakistani difficult degree which is the
First Indian Home Land in Will Want Toe
Integrate with specific song locations
Exit Point in Time to Chinese Knot
Want you will want to happen in the V channel
subscribe to
[music]
In the Taliban
Induction into conflict with
This One India Can Play in This One India
Idli and Average in
Afghanistan-Taliban
Subscribe
long-term play what is the
Biggest
I don't want to see the
World in the World
The question is, Pant is the Taliban
Guruji anti China in Pakistan where in
India will have to plane this last year
China also included America in this and city 4592
Deposits in time to be dissolved long-term
Objective What Mean Singh Right Knowledge of
Day to day work hand of unfolding of
Events with real games long-term it is the
The Kid with the Real Question Is Not Be Amazing
wicket next two days video chinese want
United what is Taliban want what is
India wants to achieve additional long-term real
The game is played for a long-term in India
There are actually more levels in China.
Taliban has fought till the last
loot
Arun Bhai Size is capturing Afghanistan
Taliban is help in the world for
Starting the next version of World Wide
And will this friendship between lines
Taliban Help China Peek in the Next
World Power So I Don't See Reactive
Vasundha Sun this is it not want to be
Beneficial for any body world wide
Destructive and People Want to Protect
Ther Investments World Vas
Distorted Destroys Investment Secretary
and Novels of Friendship Between Taliban
Pakistan Helpline is still an underworld power
Tariffs on Friendship in Politics Raisen
Times Now Only Temporary Alliance Is Here
Convergence and research in which how is it made
Lines with a temporary internet connection
Drivers and the rest of the world
Changed hiss
And Sudesh A you relationship this hunger
The relationship between Noida and Taliban is
Mode of China Using Taliban
long-term political activities and
used tow
Get Into What You Need To
Give something in return for display on
Friendship Inn
Taliban Afghanistan Just a Small Piece of
Global
Power
power production
Today, but this temple is not only two
Nuvvante speech on the test board it is
Not Gonna To Make Them World Power Taliban In
Significant Force them Noble Field
Poverty Stone Inn including Afghanistan
Forest Country Very Small Minor Country
Won the Global Your Political Chess Board
Sundha Advance Channels Strategy One Who
Protects all it is it is not under 19
world power word power take off time
Planning lot of implementation in which
Is the time of birth of tears to it all
of disinvestment Diana Hayden in various
Spheres Which Is
A Possible To Make China World Power Itself
Difficult You
Ok
Taliban Pakistan Home Friends If
Taliban
Widening of events and Pakistan IS
hidden episode
From This Is The Answer Is Pakistan
repeat
Friendship in Politics
Taliban and if Pakistani cricketer
Dhapali in the expendables school in ther
long-term game in the long term end
The long term objective of India was
Pakistan Army Festival
Finger One Option
Retention all encompassing all comes under
Observation is India India is the best
Price wants to talk India ODI in flight
The flying from Red Fort that is there
objective the problem Kashmir Kashmir is the
Real Problem Universe India Hands and
Pakistan makes Kashmir divine
2858 Chakli Somebody Like Manmohan Singh For
Example where to hand over Kashmir milk
Pakistani is the Pakistani name on this broad
Vikram Friends India was old one month
Because objectives to destroy India
As long as India is somewhere in the
country.the Pakistani spinner thandi
Pakistan Army Officer Turned End the Day
Pottery India is the Enemy's But Gives Little
Machine with Pakistan and made them in power
should have created this tool cold Delhi
dam
The British media power governs the Pashtun people
Hua Today 740 Expandable Edition Matter How
Many Bones Diary Pakistani Don't Care To
Pakistanis want to fight India
Using back plan was to fight India to
Lead India Way Taliban
Subjective Taliban want to create and
Islamist organizations which will
Eventualy Target India and A Plus Two
Use Afghanistan Force per
Begusarai Devoted Toe Fight Indian Rural
Life is the current affair not appointed a
Taliban from college Madras state in which
Is residing now ₹10 What happened was the
Creating an Editor
Taliban in Pashtun Definitely Islamic
Taliban Bigg Boss and Pashtun positive
Almost exclusively for stool and
Details given rise to personal album and
Happy Life is Not Exactly Glue
Inspection Pakistan ISI Submit Wanted
to go on with a water in them to have only
Islamic ID is widely distributed among Taliban
Strong Pashtun Identity
Interested Very Strongly Anti Punjab
straight when there's a long history behind this tho
Stones on Its History The First Bay
Converted to Islam in India on
but in Bandha and in Northern India
should be converted to Islam and
Distorted Launching Reddy Into India
With and is the Governor Owes in the blood India
Sale More Properties Genocide in India
Cultural Genocide A message read to millions of
Indians which includes Punjabi is the Punjabi
Board the front to great extent of this
Pashtun Inventions of Ginger Unwanted
Ninth Choli The Punjabi Mother Goat Converted Toe
Islam But Is
in the video
Stones Punjab
School
Maharaja Ranjit Singh
Ranjit Singh Dates True Lies
In His Daughter Of
today's pakistan border
But
Pakistan has
Between Pakistan and Meenakshi Sinha
Army Shuddh Usko have this incident and
Witty method Pashtun even milk both sides of
Muslims Today Its
Pimple Blood Animated Like The Italian
Vendetta with Golden for Generations After
Generation
Shoaib Pakistan is the Pakistan Army
Punjab and beam create this Taliban force to
Believe in India but
Sacrifice Famous Punjabi Bhej Do
Pakistani this
If so, then that judgmental behavior from the Taliban is cheap.
Cheap you want to understand the old ignore
Words Learn Questions
Only See Actions Ward Tamil Politician
Organ Jobs Will Make More Cancer Promise
Welcome to Buddha's first promise is a that matter
Realization Cheap Ignore Words Focus on the Missions
Now coming months coming years will this
Award Taliban Truly and Pakistan
Taliban is 121 choli abs Punjab Pakistan
Army Way
Taliban Pakistan
Today Pakistan
Politics Very Old Blood
Punjabi Suit
This is not going to be the IS side in
Miscellaneous Hotspot On
A
Question Pakistan has been double price in
USA Today One Credit Also Possible If
Yasmin Patience Taliban Two Box Nice
Pakistan since its root cause of the
Problem or it's just wishful thinking straight
Americans New Very Well Worthy Pakistanis
Drawing Presentation Double Crossing
Institute of Design to 10th New
Pakistanis Separate But I Don't See The New
Even during the day, there is a rap scene dealing with Pakistanis.
Is Well in Vernocular but Afghanistan Will
Wipe out the Taliban toe sanctions from
Afghanistan but will love you to create her
Peeth and Guys if Taliban in Partnership
with Pakistan
Chaudhary Audio Political Objectives Are
Fulfilled with long term kisses also like bell
Button America in Pakistan and abroad
In alert Pakistani is painted old
Taliban Day Pakistan Even Though It Was
Caught cheating on American soldiers
That Hero Soldier Had Just Came Under the
The Expendables Matter Shouldn't Very Much S
possible to see it's properly agreement of
Owning a Pakistani-American is back in time
Naughty Americans in verification the world is
Different
Videos want to punish India the time for
Going toe clear in the 2nd world has changed
A Lot in America's Geopolitical
Objectives of very different reverse
Pakistan has gone to the Chinese camp
ekdum eric servant se pakistan s usefull
This useful temporary in Allah edit also
Alloy Drop Shot Birthday America Sub Naval
Version Pakistan Preserve Trust in which
Politics
Research Today Pakistan has gone to Chinese
Cambridge Americans Will Not Be Very
Pledged support u PM the
Pakistan Code and Becoming a Valuable Asset
China with Chinese will want to access the
Water for the Indian Ocean via Pakistan
David Warner Pakistan Economic Order of
Producer lines with Pakistan is bell
Strength in China China last second with
Chinese want to use Afghanistan editor
Transit Route for the Best End Roads
infrastructure
American Scotty and Focusing Morale tomorrow morning
China Development Channelizing Noble Competitiveness
American
Diamond Discus Before the Two Side Sprouts
Dhawan and existing regiments power is
Confronted with the rise of new is when in
Power Din Voice Almost Inevitable Dharsira
Destroyed were the Americans' planning too.
for long term
For possibly inventive with Chinese and two
Loose channel products were order to support
Research Labs in Rose Road Infrastructure
The China Pakistan Economic Author Cross Over
All the best dress
Start New Civil War 10 We Use In The
Taliban Usually Pakistani Taliban
Stoves Possible in Destabilized Pakistan
Even for beginners Pakistan, it is the
Possibility is not saying this was
Happening I am not prevent water Shravan you
Ones of thinking and worked with Susser
definitely possibly of course not the
American shirt seriously fearing threat and
By the rise of China so objections and
so called
Withdraw from Afghanistan it is the
Price willin toe play the willin toe pay the
Price of looking at any cost for much
Bigger long-term political executive
which is the what is the
Possibility
We Should Not Discount America in Want to
from Pakistan
vid oo
loot 100 vaccine earth if indian
Government Use Taliban Department
Pakistani Singur land line this matter but
Nothing should only be a temporary thing
Agreement is like Taliban, remind set
A sweater voice of research and future will
Start from India, can you see it?
Politics
I will temporarily divide my friendship.
Alliance
10 Lines About Have Been a Temporary
Arrangement The American Alliance Pakistan
War Temple Reliance Today Pakistan
America Servant Allied Pakistani Simple Design
In India and where honey is long long
Standings
Strategic Alliances Today Indian Russia Now
Longer Life in the Same Manner
Yo Yo Honey American Bean used in the
Taliban, Tere Bin Laden, Al Qaeda in Iran
In Iraq and Syria, the Dewar News Eye System
Point in Time: Major and Temporary
Arrangements to Achieve Short Term
Geopolitical Objectives
So if India Taliban have seen that
Pakistan I don't see any reason why
India should not temporarily use this
Terrorist Outfit Against Pakistan
Pakistani all u centers and how again
India for decades has just what it is.
Good Advice for Indian Rupee Back
Pakistan End Assembly Session Coin
So I am not against India
Are you using Taliban silk as a temporary
Tool against Pakistan why not it is
Relating to Taking Everything in a Positive Way
Should
Do Not Criticize
Pakistani
Change Use Terrorists Department at
Home with
Pakistan
End
Cultural and they can only be
used
Tow Bay Temporarily
possibility of
A
Swastika soil as you said you should be the
Beginning and end Pakistan where is
The question is, it is, that is in the near future.
Pakistan during recent visit in showpiece
Invest in shares in your heart what will
happen if the is there any chance of threat to
India is informed that Taliban is sticking to China
Plots Videos Next Step BCR
Fruitive Actions Security in Future
Administrators Pakistan Video
Subscribe Nuclear Weapons
Subscribe
2nd T20
Pakistan Beat India
Subscribe The Channel
Delivery mechanisms of
A second thing is a condition greater than another
Deal of clans you want to have a stable
If you become a government you will have great difficulties.
Mother India has two drops of Pilo Pilo
Officer of the Pakistan Nation
Depression beckons a bunch of modelers and nations
In definition, jore will definitely be a
Period of instability in every five
Years and years on India will have to be
Taken to prepare for the India's defence
Forces will be off but for all fans of events
Qualities but what India Industries
Page Should Happen in Farming Stable
Democratic and Peaceful Government
Subject with Long Term Objective Snake
Step-by-step instructions were punished
Secure the Nuclear Weapons and Remember
Faux Office Late Difficult * Is Not Like
Here on Play Button Powertrain for Souda
Physics Chapter India would-be 1 inch
Sachin Adventurous A
Ayub Scam Religious Religions Make a Comeback
in Afghanistan Pakistan next years
no no
It took 58 years for Indian culture with religion
No Tubelight Don't of Afghanistan
in Pakistan
that take of information act this point to
Thousand Years in Office Arrival Powder
Dwivedi is Hindu and Six Loop
The Pure Process Back to Thousand Years
Can Be Revised in Fifty Years
So I don't see my comeback of the religious
Festivals in Pakistan and Gandhara, Afghanistan
in 10 years
I give up hope this has to be
Combining to Generation Positive India has to
Create recreate if lions of like
Like-Minded Nations Wheat Seed and Lost Territory
I Don't See Anything Wrong But India The
Aspiring To Reclaim Destroys One Day
Garland
Sufficiently and cultured back into Indian
culture
Early morning long-term project The Chinese
Plan for hundreds of years ago much
Older
Pimple of two or three years but not in every
generation so that this control plane that
Effigy of Thought Farukh Multi Generation Hot Look
Plain Ways Can Work to That But Certainly Not
going to happen next year he definitely was too
Tech Long Latest Updates Step by Step
Slow a Gradual Process: Fix and Do Not
Believe In
Converting Mother Sons
Died So Wicked
of
Swami from Culture It's Hard for Me
Indians to distinguish between watching real
And Why Not Let's Finally Stupid People
Tried to apply spirituality in
Worldly Affairs and Meditative 10 Simply
Call Mechanic Inspires 68 People
Electronic names given to connect with
Heart for Indian social reality see I don't
Blame the people of India for having a
Sort of mind set it is from India
Education System Debt The India Backem
Independent Beach and Non-Violence End
Satyagraha is Mohandas Gandhi
Indians to Liberate Developed Water Teachers
Three teachers are banyan trees, teachers when you
Grow fonder than this
Thrill Been Told This Year After Year You
Don't Stop Believing That School
brainwashing
The Indians truly believe in its non-violence
Fall and Satyagraha Mind Mohandas Gandhi
Robert Freedom Indore for this tool morning
Used Oil Situations
Indian and not able to see and finally Bigg
Boss Indian Education System It It
Also prevent when we ask obscene questions
It is not in use in the map of India with the
Increase Critical Thinking Process Knowledge
For Indians
Believe Media
Monitoring
Misled and Dark What You Really Works
Best with
Violence Acid
Violence Bill to Give Freedom
non-violence gives you freedom and
Independence Transfer and
Subscribe
100 Questions and Answers in the World in
Superintendent I
New for fact that Indians and naturally
Intelligent People India The Most Brilliant
and Intelligent People Babul World
302 120 Explain properly while the
Most People Actually Understand What Will
Happen In
Sudhir and today able to distinguish
Between Madurai and Notifications and Intire
system where is the education system madrasa
Teachers, Professors, Universities, Colleges with
The media is selling politicians hair oil
Telling Slice Bapu gave us freedom
Water and fruit non-sense
Soye Indians of waking up today it will
Tech Time Mixer Gradual Process To Tech
A couple of generations but today
Generation Today Youngsters and Much Wider in Much
Better Informed Strong Parents Process
You have taken time but I think India will soon
Becoming a More Realistic Nation
that Uttarakhand Anderson is Reebok Once Started
approaching one stopping the mindset and
Approach of All Great Guru Vishnu Gupta
Chanakya President One India will start to
Interruption in the population The population of
India Has To Do
and embody the teachings of great Guru
Vishnu Gupta Chanakya
surrender
5803 Quality Happening to Certain Extent
Hero Just
Gather Peace Epps Gomez
that your this is the set for today
Electrification Live Questions From You
Sharif Solvent Have Any Questions Class
In Ashtami no I will take few questions
That from your Anurag, Sweetu first look for
Tenth Million Dollar Economy You Are Right
Economy 10 Matter What This Movie Scenes
Foreign which makes the roots much smaller than before
Friends and Attractions are really powerful.
Military is its defacto super power
Leaders should not sleep for 20 minutes. Economic
Dress matter is developed India when population
Will need red chilli glance economical haze
Gradual Tubelight Global Peace Marine
Commando Bal Your Political Player You Only
Have to investor fuel end per 2009
Player in the Military
FD with Daily in the Vikram Global
Geopolitical Player in a Matter of Few
Years pay $10 most so yes economic dust
Hosts The Companies Use Rose
Hot power of their overall
comprehensive national power it's definitely
Something the Indian nation today that
800 India needs to find ways of
Restarting, rebooting, and fixing this issue
Economic after particularly this and make.
Pizza Stop Loving Oo
who actually gives independence not
Bapu
width conflict
I want in defense of independence of but they
Still to be in the same loss the British route
will be considered as not one drop of
Indian culture in it is waste
Unconstitutional VR
200g System of Governance
Parliamentary democracy has been taken
Co Fit Wholesale British Westminster
system and democracy is fit and
Democracy's Growth Rate Ignores Internal
Democracy with Political Parties Only
Option digestive beer with right to vote and
once in every five years
For better institutions of co-operative nurses
police force what is Indian appointed a
best speech in english hot x in
English also off but job interviews in
English wear steel completely curved heads
Country Wear is the Independent Difference
Predicament Android based will completely
Closed Eyes On
and biofuel questions
loot
Soylent vs Randy Chand Chanel Day
Celebrate It's Very Unlikely to Be Chinese
Food today cigarette distance from its very
Strong In
This is now fitting into the Ignoble Ecosystem Solid
is very unlikely
For Chinese Communist Party Indore
Regret, of course, it can happen strangely.
Things Happen Unlikely Things Happen So One
Has to understand what the point blank
against pain points
Looks and patterns recorded through out Chinese
Street Give What Happens for the Condition
Chakli doodhi kal of dream so this milk is cord
The Diagnostic Cycles Is Spoken
Words Before Due To It's Different
Likely the Chinese Communist Party
Indulge in some
Misadventure Specially Now Military Midwinter
that in which your defense accounts to defeat
Half an hour electricity possibly to
This period depends on the condition level
Disintegration of the Communist Party to
Have a Responsibility But It Is
Unlikely It Is Highly Unlikely But Not
Impossible
ok all more questions
This scene is from Siddha Alliance Gates Anil Ibadat
Taliban will the world just watch with you in
Next on it is not done Reliance Gas
Anite World Will Sit and Watch and Give
Women involved in at the long and short of it
But nobody will lift figure to stop the
Taliban was denied international languages
Unlikely is a good team and every day
Points in alarms Taliban it is
Possible body covered very good difference
Strong Hold It Is Pet Is Naturally Good
For defense cooperation is it and high
Mountains in a very small valley between
Pollution River Which Very Hard For Indian
Weddings for Special Years of Primitive
Form Sutherland Taliban to Call Karo Region
If this seems like the longest subject to alarms gas
Supply Capacity GK Products and Damage
Able to Withstand Taliban
should be able to linger inside for a long time
Prabhu Certificate Unit Taliban dw.de
OK Lakshmi Test One More Question A
Question Saurabh, the reason behind politics
Lut tan message what is the reason for Lut da
Bangladeshis Head Towards India
Religion and culture are simple
that thief recommended reading material after
Teachings of the Great Guru Vishnu
Key Reed Economics Available Online
Intervene in relation possibly across languages
toe read this is not a job toe read with tex
Time To Read Joe Read 16 Times Ahead Guys
Now this year there was no one before only hammers
Tutorials That They DFE Understand
Teachings of this great man
that you have one more question
Loot Horses India Supportive Line
Secretly it is possible if Indian
Government will support Northern Alliance it is
in India and pressed for the per
Taliban to take over the country in the
Early Completely Should Always Be Up End
Points for the voices of the Taliban
India should never trust the Taliban 99
One India Hindi Fearsome Point Time Worked
With
Amazing with big boobs pressed against witch
can certainly used in that then the second equal
Average Vipin Adhin The Always Best Idris
that returns to the Taliban from within
His research on it's good for India then
Northern alarms is equal to whole don't
Indrajal Wali 100 is India supplying
Nobel Prize but the government has not
Disclose Any Thing It Is Not Impossible
In India Without It's Possible But David
You that 2019 real guide secret of
Okay habit se today tho most words great
Thank you for your questions.
for watching
I appreciate it, thank you very much and I will
See You in Tomorrow's Live Session Final Day Tech
Care have a good have good night my